Using Python 3.9.11 (version may not matter)

Create a virtual environment by calling "py -m venv .venv", activate it using "./.venv/Scripts/activate", and deactivate it by calling "deactivate"

Do "py -m pip install --upgrade pip" first

Run these to install the necessary packages
py -m pip install numpy
py -m pip install chakin
py -m pip install tensorflow
py -m pip install ipykernel

Run this to activate the Jupyter Notebook kernel
py -m ipykernel install --user --name=glove

With the .ipynb file open, press Ctrl + Shift + P and search for "Preferences: Open User Settings"
Go to the Extensions section
Go to the Python subsection
Enter the path to your virtual environment's scripts folder in "Default Interpreter Path".
For me, it is "C:\Users\964864\OneDrive - Cognizant HealthCare\Documents\Innovation Project\Unified GloVe\.venv\Scripts"
Go back to the .ipynb file and click on the button at the top right to select a kernel
Select "Python Environments..." (There might be another step before here. If so, select the option to find another kernel, or something like that)
Select the kernel in the .venv folder you just made